cyberwealth7.com 2014-03-27

# TERMS OF SOFTWARE USE

TERMS OF SOFTWARE USE
Cyber Wealth 7, a division of Cyber Wealth Alliance, Inc., hereinafter referred to as, CWA, Inc., provides its
clients with a 7 DAY unconditional satisfaction guarantee for its CFA GUARDIAN Cyber Security software suite.
If you are dissatisfied for any reason, your monthly software license fee and download fee will be fully refunded.
Purchaser further agrees that after the 7 DAY satisfaction guarantee, THERE ARE ABSLOUTELY NO
REFUNDS! IF PURCHASER USED A CREDIT CARD TO PURCHASE SOFTWARE, PURCHASER IRREVOCABLY
AGREES TO NEVER INITIATE A CHARGEBACK AGAINST CWA, Inc.
If Purchaser chooses to discontinue paying the Month-To-Month software use license fee, An E-mailed
cancellation request must be provided no fewer than 15 days prior to current software expiration date
to: cancelmysubscription@cyberwealth7.net.
License: CWA, Inc., grants to the registered individual and or Business entity, (“Licensee”) a non-exclusive license
to use the Software solely for its intended purpose on a month to month basis and for the number of
computers/workstations selected. Title and all ownership and proprietary rights to the Software remain the
property of CWA, Inc.
PRIVACY POLICY
    CWA, Inc 's privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers the collection and use of personal information ("Personal
    Information") that we may gather any time you interact with us, such as when you visit our Web site, demo
    our products, purchase CWA, Inc. products, or when you call our customer support or sales departments.
    This policy describes our data privacy practices, including what type of information is gathered, how CWA,
    Inc., uses the information, and how we safeguard your Personal Information.
    AT CWA, INC., PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US. AFTER ALL, ONLINE PRIVACY
    AND SECURITY IS WHAT WE'RE ALL ABOUT.
    You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.
    Personal Information may be processed by CWA, Inc. in the country where it was collected as well as other
    countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less
    stringent.
    WHY CWA, INC. COLLECTS PERSONAL INFORMATION
    CWA, Inc. only collects your Personal Information where it is required to provide you products or services
    which you request such as additional documents, demonstrations of our software, or sales orders. By
    maintaining an accurate customer database, we are able to send notifications via e-mail to keep you
    informed about the status of our products and to provide updates and technical notices.
    WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
    CWA, Inc. collects your Personal Information at a variety of points, including when you place an order
    through our e-Commerce provider Solid Trust Pay, register software, request services or take part in other
    activities on our Web site. For example, we often ask for your Personal Information when you are looking to
    demo our technology, conferring with one of our customer support technicians, downloading a new product
    or program update, registering your software or purchasing a product. During these interactions we will
    collect Personal Information relevant to your transacting with CWA, Inc. such as your name, mailing

address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information, or when you are doing a demo your
information about the CWA, Inc. products you own or use, such as the activation code or key code, date of
purchase and information relating to a support issue.
Please be aware that if you prefer not to provide us with your Personal Information, because such
information may be necessary for us to provide certain services, we may not be able to, or may choose not
to, make such services available to you.
REGARDING CHILDREN
CWA, Inc. does not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13.
COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES
Following common e-commerce practices, CWA, Inc. uses "cookies" and other technologies to collect non-
personal data that enables us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and
effectiveness of CWA, Inc.’s Cyber Wealth 7 Web sites. Cookies are unique text files sent to your browser
and stored on your computer.
If you do not want CWA, Inc. to send cookies to your browser, you can set your browser options to reject
cookies or notify you when a Web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Rejecting cookies may
affect your ability to use some of our Web site services.
Additionally, CWA, Inc. gathers general information about visits to our Web site and stores this information
in log files. This information is stored in anonymous profiles and is not associated with a user's account.
This information includes the number of total visits to our Web site, and which browser is used to view our
Web site (including the version number). No Personal Information is contained in this data. CWA, Inc. uses
this information to understand traffic and downloads on our Web site, enabling us to improve the site,
provide the best online experience possible and improve our ability to serve our customers.
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
CWA, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. CWA, Inc. will not, under any circumstances, rent or sell
your Personal Information nor does CWA, Inc. trade or exchange mailing lists with any other organization.
Furthermore, CWA, Inc. only shares your Personal Information with our contractors that assist us in our
efforts to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners that commit to adhere to the same level
of commitment as CWA, Inc. to protect your privacy and data. CWA, Inc. maintains this information; but we
may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we believe that such action is necessary to (1)
comply with the law; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of CWA, Inc.; (3) enforce the CWA, Inc.
Terms of Service Agreement; or (4) protect the safety of any individual or the general public.
CWA, INC. / CYBER WEALTH 7 AFFILIATES
CWA, Inc. may share some or all of your Personal Information with any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or
other companies under a common control (collectively, "affiliates"), in which case we will require our

affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that
company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations
regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.
HOW WE COMMUNICATE WITH YOU
CWA, Inc. may have an optional e-mail service for customers who wish to periodically receive promotional
information, such as general product, service and CWA, Inc. news. Customers are provided the option to
opt-out within each e-mail. If you no longer wish to receive CWA, Inc. communications, you may
"unsubscribe" from our mailing program at any time in the following ways:
      By clicking on the auto-unsubscribe link included in each e-mail
      By contacting our customer support department via FAX at 1-559-765-4987, via direct mail to CWA, Inc.,
       777 Minnewawa Ave. Suite 3 Clovis, CA 93612 USA or e-mail to: cs@cyberwealth7.net or via our online
       ticketed support system: http://www.cyberwealth7.com/support.php
We will then update our database and take reasonable measures so that no further promotional
correspondence should be sent to the e-mail address. You may, however, still receive transactional
messages.
TRANSACTIONAL MESSAGES
CWA, Inc. may send required notifications via e-mail to keep you informed of the status of your orders or
accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. This service is used for messages that are important
for the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our services. When you purchase or
register a product online, we require an e-mail address for completion of the transaction, which we will use
for these communications.
WAYS TO UPDATE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
CWA, Inc. carefully maintains our customer database in an effort to keep your Personal Information
accurate for the purposes for which it is used. It is your right to be able to update your Personal
Information as needed. You can correct out-of-date information, update information, remove information or
review any information previously provided to CWA, Inc. by contacting our customer support department
via FAX at 1-559-765-4987, via direct mail to CWA, Inc., 777 Minnewawa Ave. Suite 3 Clovis, CA 93612
USA or e-mail to: cs@cyberwealth7.net or via our online ticketed support system:
http://www.cyberwealth7.com/support.php Please note, however, we may retain certain information
relating to software licensing and your information may also be retained in our archives. When contacting
our customer service, we will verify your identification through the use of security questions before sharing
any Personal Information as it appears in our customer database.
CWA, INC.'S COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY
CWA, Inc. has security measures in place, such as the following, to protect against the loss, misuse and
alteration of your Personal Information in our customer database. Personal Information provided to CWA, Inc.
is stored in secure facilities with access restricted to authorized personnel only. We have put in place a

series of access-control procedures required for retrieval of personal information. The CWA, Inc. Cyber
Wealth 7 Web site is regularly tested for security breaches to protect against unauthorized viewing of
Personal Information.
To provide secure credit card processing when ordering, orders placed through our Web site are processed
through a payment gateway which operates under its own privacy policy.
CWA, Inc. DOES NOT store credit card information. If you choose to purchase the software online using a
credit card, the credit card information is sent to solid Trust Pay using SSL (Secure Socket Layer)
encryption, an industry-standard method for protecting data as it travels over the Internet. If at any time
you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, follow
the "Customer Service" link in the shopping cart checkout page. There you will find information for placing
your order via phone, fax, or regular mail.
Although we make good faith efforts to store the Personal Information we collect in a secure operating
environment that is not accessible to unauthorized users, we cannot guarantee complete security.
ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY
By using the Web site or any services provided through the Web site, you expressly consent to the use and
disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy.
PRIVACY POLICY REVISIONS
CWA, Inc. reserves the right to amend, revise or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements
at any time and in any manner. Any revisions, amendment or modification will be posted on the
www.cyberwealth7.com website.
Cyber Wealth Alliance, Inc. Contact information:
inquiry@cyberwealthalliance.com
SEND ALL OTHER CORRESPONDENCE TO:
CWA, Inc.
777 Minnewawa Ave. Suite 3 Clovis, CA 93612 USA
If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily
addressed, you should contact CWA, Inc. through the online support ticket system @
http://www.cyberwealth7.com/support.php or by calling 1-877-713-7115.
Effective 03/23/2013 the CWA, Inc. privacy statement disclosures were updated.
